Guide to the Vassar College Student Materials Collection, 1859-2025 (bulk 1867-1950)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES VI. NOTEBOOKS, 1866-1974
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — [Geology], undated (Box 158)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Art, undated (Box 159)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Psychology Lab, undated (Box 159)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Chemistry, undated (Box 160)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Art, undated (Box 160)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Miscellaneous, undated (Box 160)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Economics, undated (Box 160)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Chorites and Corrections, undated (Box 160)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Ethical Sys. Syllabus, undated (Box 160)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — House Sanitation, undated (Box 161)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Norwegian Costume, undated (Box 161)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Hygiene and Psychology, undated (Box 161)
  - VC 1911 — McDonnell, Irene (Palmer) — Geology, undated (Box 99)
  - VC Ex 1911 — Lowell, Gladys M. (Ballou) — Rhetoric and Composition (predates Vassar years), 1904-1905 (Box 116)
  - VC 1912 — Miss 1912 — Latin, circa 1908 (Box 204)
  - VC Ex 1912 — Townsend, Louise — Apostolic Age, 1908-[1911?] (Box 204)
  - VC 1913 — Dodge, Elizabeth — Music, 1911 (Box 98)
  - VC 1913 — Hopkins, Gladys Eugenia (Hull) — Medieval History, undated (Box 114)
  - VC 1913 — Hopkins, Gladys Eugenia (Hull) — 4 Bible, undated (Box 98)
  - VC 1913 — Hull, Gladys Eugenia — 4 Bible, undated (Box 98)
  - VC 1914 — West, Laura S. — Notebook, 1912 (Box 213)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Chemistry, 1913 (Box 53)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Chemistry, [1913?] September 26 - [1914?] March 6 (Box 53)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — History, 1914 March 3 (Box 53)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Philosophy, 1913 September - 1914 January (Box 53)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Philosophy, 1914 January 12 (Box 53)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Religion, undated (Box 53)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — American History, undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — "Calliorus and Nullification", undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Geometry, undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Economics, undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — English J and JJ, undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — "...Profit Sharing", undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — US History, undated (Box 54)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — French, undated (Box 55)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — French, undated (Box 55)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — French, [1913?] November 22 - [1914?] January (Box 55)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — History, undated (Box 55)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — History, undated (Box 55)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — "Introspection on Pressure Spots", undated (Box 55)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Biographies, undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — "Chrono Outline 19th century Literature", undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Communication Make the Festivals Possible...", undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — English Literature, undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — "Modern Means of Power of Parliament", undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Psychology, undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Psychology, undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Psychology – lab, undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Sociology, undated (Box 56)
  - VC 1916 — Farnham, Gertrude — Geology (photocards, some annotated), circa 1912-1916 (Box 207)
  - VC 1917 — Lyday, June — Economics, 1915-1916 (Box 116)
  - VC 1917 — Thorp, Anne — Economics, 1915-1916 (Box 116)
  - VC 1924 — Hedrick, Eleanor — Economics (Box 116)
  - VC 1924 — Russell, Jeanne — Economics (Box 116)
  - VC 1924 — Stone, Mildred — Economics, undated (Box 116)
  - VC 1924 — Stone, Mildred — Psychology [Psych 101?], reading notes on "Mary Lamb and Her Brother" and "Resemblance of Twins,", circa 1923 (Box 213)
  - VC 1925 — Meyers, Florence (White) — Botany, undated (Box 177)
  - VC 1926 — Clothier, Florence — Economics [scrapbook], undated (Box 115)
  - VC 1926 — Driver, Ruth — Economics [scrapbook], undated (Box 115)
  - VC 1931 — Squire, Marjorie (Hurlburt) — 3 Bacteriology, undated (Box 191)
  - VC 1931 — Squire, Marjorie (Hurlburt) — Histology, undated (Box 191)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — English [Senior Project], 1934-1935 (Box 104)
  - VC 1937 — Chapin, Virginia — Music 140, 1936-1937 (Box 196)
  - VC 1938 — King, Gertrude — German, undated (Box 161)
  - VC 1939 — Morton, Frankie P. (Davis) — Astronomy, 1935-1936 (Box 97)
  - VC 1940 — Dain, Katherine — Music 140, 1937-1938 (Box 207)
  - VC 1940 — Dain, Katherine — Music 340, 1938-1939 (Box 207)
  - VC 1940 — Dain, Katherine — Primitive Drama, circa 1936-1940 (Box 207)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — English, Latin, and Music, 1945-1950 (Box 212)
  - VC 1957 — Allen, Helen — History with Carl Degler, 1953-1954 (Box 196)
  - VC 1950 — Showker, Selwa — History, circa 1948-1950 (Boxes 183-184)
  - VC 1950 — Curtis, Charlotte, circa 1946-1950 (Boxes 201-202)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — English, 1956-1957 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — Religion, 1957-1958 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — Interdepartmental, 1957-1958 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — Art History, 1957-1958 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — History, 1957-1960 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — French, 1957-1960 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — Political Science, 1958-1959 (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — Music, undated (Box 178)
  - VC 1960 — Hoyt, Sarnia (Hayes) — Economics, undated (Box 178)
  - VC 1961 — Korzenik, Diana — Philosophy 110a, 1958 (Box 205)
  - VC 1961 — Korzenik, Diana — Philosophy 110b, 1959 (Box 205)
  - VC 1961 — Korzenik, Diana — Religion 120a, 1958 (Box 205)
  - VC 1961 — Korzenik, Diana — unidentified, circa 1959 (Box 205)
  - VC 1961 — Page, Joan — Plant Science [281], 1958-1959 (Box 105)
  - VC 1971 — Casteras, Susan P. — Art History, English, Philosophy, Psychology, circa 1967-1971 (Box 208)
  - VC 1974 — Houghtaling, Christina — Art 241 (Box 208)
  - Unidentified — Botany Samples, 1866-1871 (Box 117)
  - Unidentified — Trigonometry, 1868 (Box 104)
  - Unidentified — Art [Prof Henry Van Ingen], 1885 (Box 93)
  - Unidentified — I. Music Notes, 1904 (Box 204)
  - Unidentified — II. Music Notes, C Art (completed), 1904 (Box 204)
  - Unidentified — C Art, 1904 (Box 204)
  - Unidentified — D Art, 1905 (Box 204)
  - Unidentified — Philosophy A, 1905 (Box 114)
  - Unidentified — Art History, circa 1905 (Box 206)
  - Unidentified — [Ruth?] — Shakespeare, 1906 (Box 204)
  - Unidentified — English 105, 1947-1948 (Box 99)
- SERIES VII. NOTECARDS, circa 1897 - circa 1950
  - VC 1897 — Chesley, Mabel — American History - Constitutional History, undated (Boxes 136-137)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — European History/ Saxon Literature, Prof. Ida Thallon, 1908 (Box 77)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — The Causes of the American Revolution/ An analysis of Burke speech on conciliation with American and Declaration of Independence, Prof. Lois Kimball Matthews, 1909 (Box 77)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — The Causes of the American Revolution/ The Council of Trent, 1909 (Box 77)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "R" Ethnic Elements in American History/ The Contributions of Foreigners to American Music, Prof. Lucy Salmon, 1910 (Box 77)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Materials/ Records of Nature Which Throw Light on the History of the U.S., Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 78)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Material Unwritten/What May be learned of the History of Poughkeepsie from a study of Main St., Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 77)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Materials/ Saint Valentine's Day as a Record, Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 78)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Materials/ The Historical Record Made by Names of Towns on the Railroads of Central and Northern NY, Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 78)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Materials/ The Legend of Lohengrin as a Historical Record, Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 78)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Materials/ Tudor England, as Recorded in As You Like It and King Lear, Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 78)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History "S" Historical Materials/ John Richard Green- Letters, Prof. Lucy Salmon (Box 78)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart) — Costume in England Under the Stuarts (Box 76)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart) — Paintings of the British National Gallery as History (Box 76)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart) — Gregory the Great, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Why the Irish Left Home and Why They Came to America, 1912 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Charter of Maryland, 1912 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — The Struggle for Supremacy in America as shown by the Colonial Wars, 1912 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Savonarola as a reformer, 1912 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Alexander Hamilton's Financial Policy, 1913 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — John Brown's Raid at Harper's Ferry, 1913 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — The Secession Movement in Georgia, 1913 (Box 147)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — The Tariff from 1816-1832, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — An Attempt to Give...the Points of View of the English concerning... America previous to the Revolution, undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Bibliography for Reconstruction, undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Causes of the Mexican War, undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Development of the Govt of New York State, undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Evidences of Foreigners in America, undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Folder of Canadian Pacific Railway, undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Foreign Policy of the Federal Govt, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Leading Facts in the Constitutional History from 1779-1815, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — The Monroe Doctrine, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Quarrel Between Johnson and Congress over Reconstruction, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Reconstruction in Texas, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Peter Stuyvesant, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Four Periods of Humanistic Movement, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — The Early Career of Cromwell (Oliver), undated (Box 148)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Mirabeau and the Revolution, undated (Box 149)
  - VC 1917 — Goodrich, Anne (Swann) — History from "Life," Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1924 — Kuhs, Evelyn M. — Political Science /Legal Relations, circa 1922 (Box 137)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - The Ratification of the Constitution in Maryland, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - Representation in Parliament in the Time of the American Revolution, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - Compromise of 1850, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - Deo Favente, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - The Failure of the Dutch in New Netherland, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - The Farming Frontier in Massachusetts and Survivals, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - The Indented [sic] Servant in the Middle Colonies, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - Monroe's First Mission to France. 1794-1796, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - The Northern Boundry of Minnesota, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — American History - The Spoils System, Prof. Lucy Salmon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — European History - Benvenuto Cellini, Prof. Ida Thallon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — European History - The Conversion of England from Coming of St. Augustine to the Council of Whitby, Prof. Ida Thallon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — European History - The Fourth Crusade, Prof. Ida Thallon, undated (Box 76)
  - VC 1950 — Curtis, Charlotte, circa 1946-1950 (Boxes 201-202)
- SERIES VIII. PAPERS, 1860-1984
  - VC 1865-1866 [Special] — Frost, Mary Louise — "Vassar Female College", undated (Box 155)
  - VC 1867 — McGraw, Maria (Dickinson) — 4 unidentified (prior to VC), 1860 (Box 80)
  - VC 1867 — McGraw, Maria (Dickinson) — "Cardinal Wolsey", 1866 (Box 80)
  - VC 1867 — McGraw, Maria (Dickinson) — 2 unidentified, 1866, undated (Box 80)
  - VC Ex 1875 — Pidgeon, Mary (Kiersted) — unidentified, undated (Box 80)
  - VC Ex 1877 — Webb, Ella C — unidentified, circa 1872-1876 (Box 83)
  - VC 1883 — Fearrington, Mary (Pass) — Latin, undated (Box 80)
  - VC 1883-1884 [Special] — Barned, Harriet I. — [English?], undated (Box 209)
  - VC 1887 — Stewart, Ella (Wilson)— 5 English, 1883-1885 (Box 80)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Life of Julius Caesar" — History, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Caesar and Brutus" — English, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Relation of Animal to Human Instinct" — [Psychology?], undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "The Durable Satisfactions of Life", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Beginnings Great and Small", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Mediaeval Universities", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "The Trinity Lemon Squeezer", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Wagner's Reformations of the Opera", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "The Roman Villa in Caesar's Time", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — "Should Feeing be Encouraged in the United States?", undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — Unidentified, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1900 — Long, Harriet B. — Influence, 1893 (Box 203)
  - VC 1909 — Milholland, Inez — "Robert Owen's Materialistic Interpretation of History", undated (Box 92)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Religion, undated (Box 151)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Philosophy, undated (Box 151)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 2 English, undated (Box 151)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 2 Sociology, undated (Box 151)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 2 Psychology, undated (Box 151)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 2 History, undated (Box 151)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — French, undated (Box 152)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Psychology, undated (Box 152)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Psych and Ed, undated (Box 152)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Math, undated (Box 152)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 2 English, undated (Box 152)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 3 unidentified, undated (Box 152)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Chemistry, 1912-1913 (Box 150)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Philosophy, 1913 (Box 150)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — 3 English, 1914 (Box 150)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — History, 1914 (Box 150)
  - VC 1918 — Litchfield, Miriam de S.— Translation of Maeterlinck Play (Box 81)
  - VC 1920 — Wallace, Mary O. — Areopogitica by John Milton annotated by Mary O. Wallace, undated (Box 83)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay)— Economics [Econ 101 (Box 91)
  - VC 1923 — Updegraff, Ruth M.— Economics (Box 91)
  - VC 1924 — Stone, Mildred — Psychology [Psych 18: Social Psychology], Prof. Margaret F. Washburn, "The Psychology of Selling,", circa 1924 (Box 213)
  - VC 1924 — Stone, Mildred — Psychology [Psych 101: Abnormal Psychology], Prof. Margaret F. Washburn, circa 1923 (Box 213)
  - VC 1925 — Brooker, Gretta — unidentified, 1924 (Box 81)
  - VC 1925 — Hawes, Elizabeth — Economics (Box 92)
  - VC 1926 — Cole, Helen C. — 2 History, 1926, undated (Box 92)
  - VC 1932 — Campbell, M. Edwina — Religion [Rel 130], 1931 (Box 81)
  - VC 1932 — Wright, Elizabeth (Fish) — Psychology [Psych 105a, 230a, 250b, 335a], 1928-1932 (Box 207)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — unidentified, undated (Box 80)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — Psych, undated (Box 80)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — 2 English [Eng 165], undated (Box 80)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — English, undated (Box 80)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — Psych [Psych 250], 1934 (Box 80)
  - VC 1935 — Murphy, Alison B. — Philosophy [Phil 110], 1934 (Box 80)
  - VC 1935 — Wesbrook, Mary E. — History (Box 155)
  - VC 1936 — Boyd, Lola Elizabeth — 3 Philosophy [Phil 110], undated (Box 90)
  - VC 1936 — Boyd, Lola Elizabeth — 2 unidentified, 1935 (Box 90)
  - VC 1936 — Boyd, Lola Elizabeth — Poli Sci [Poli Sci 320b) (Box 90)
  - VC 1936 — Rupp, Jane (Dubbs) — Economics (Box 91)
  - VC 1938 — Acheson, Julia L. — Economics 357 (Box 82)
  - VC 1943 — MacLeod, Jean — English [Eng 405] (Box 82)
  - VC 1944 — Dimock, Lucy — History [Hist 386] (Box 82)
  - VC 1944 — Frothingham, Virginia — History (Box 80)
  - VC 1944 — Rattray, Jessica — Economics [Eco 105], circa 1944 (Box 82)
  - VC 1945 — Coffin, Harriet (Harvey) — English [Eng 312] (Box 90)
  - VC 1945 — Gilbert, Lois — History [Hist 345], 1946 (Box 80)
  - VC 1945-1944 — Schuster, Ruth — History [Hist 386] (Box 82)
  - VC 1945-1944 — Colie, Rosalie Littell — English [Eng 367] (two versions — 20 pages, 15 pages), circa 1944 (Box 207)
  - VC 1946 — Brashean, E. Lee — History (Box 82)
  - VC 1946 — Ervine, Katharine — History (Box 81)
  - VC 1946 — How, Julie — History [Hist 345] (Box 81)
  - VC 1946 — Tapley, Claire — History [Hist 345 or 355] (Box 82)
  - VC 1947 — Thompson, Jane (Fiske) — Dance [Phys Ed 380) (Box 91)
  - VC 1947-1948 — Alliot, Adele — History [Hist 355], undated (Box 82)
  - VC 1949 — Percy, Patricia — American History (Box 82)
  - VC 1950 — Curtis, Charlotte, circa 1946-1950 (Boxes 201-202)
  - VC 1950 — Vesey-Brown, Barbara — unidentified, 1947-1948 (Box 81)
  - VC 1951 — Benn, Carol (DeCamp) — English [Eng 341], 1948 (Box 91)
  - VC 1951 — Cheng, E-Su (Zen) — Economics 381, circa 1951 (Box 90)
  - VC 1951 — Cheng, E-Su (Zen) — English [Eng 312] (Box 90)
  - VC 1955 — Wilkinson, Joan (Wislocki) — Advertising [scrapbook], 1949 (Box 138)
  - VC 1957 — Goddard, Sarah — History (Box 83)
  - VC 1957 — Rockefeller, Sandra F. — History [Hist 300] (Box 81)
  - VC 1958 — Fay, Jean D. — Art [Art 300] (Box 204)
  - VC 1960 — Bosley, Anne — History [Hist 300] (Box 81)
  - VC 1961— Ellend, Nada Beth — History (Box 81)
  - VC 1963 — Feibush, Susan Beth — History [Hist 354b], 1962 (Box 80)
  - VC 1965 — Selkirk, Kathleen P. — History [Hist 300] (Box 80)
  - VC 1967 — ffolliot, Sheila — Art [Art 221a], undated (Box 204)
  - VC 1968 — Wills, Antoinette (Chwastyk) — History [Hist 234a], 1968 January (Box 92)
  - VC 1971 — Casteras, Susan P. — Art, English, History, Medieval Studies, Philosophy, Psychology, 1967-1971 (Box 209)
  - VC 1974 — Houghtaling, Christina — Art [Art 220], 1973 December (Box 204)
  - VC 1975 — Schwartz, Selde — [English], 1971 (Box 92)
  - VC 1984 — Ravicz, Elenita — History (Box 82)
  - Unidentified — Annotated List of Books in VC Library on the Dutch West India Co. and the Manor System in the Hudson River Valley, undated (Box 83)
- SERIES IX. SCRAPBOOKS (Memory Books), 1871-1963; [362 volumes]
  - VC 1870-1874 [Special]— Hastings, Alice O., 1873-1877 (Scrapbook 1)
  - VC 1870-1874 [Special]— Hastings, Alice O., 1873-1877 (Scrapbook 2)
  - VC 1875 — Barnes, Lucy (Sellers), 1872-1875 (Scrapbook 3)
  - VC Ex 1875 — Wheeler, Helen (Lough), 1871-1874 (Scrapbook 4)
  - VC 1875 — Whiting, Lillie (Lewis), 1873-1878 (Scrapbook 5)
  - VC 1876 — Lapham, Ella C., 1871-1878 (Scrapbook 6)
  - VC 1876 — Macomber, Jennie, circa 1876 (Scrapbook 214 (Oversize))
  - VC 1877 — Armstrong, Sarah (Sheppard), 1873-1890 (Scrapbook 7)
  - VC 1877 — Grant, S. Wilhelmina, circa 1877 (Scrapbook 8)
  - VC 1877 — Jacobs, Rachel B., 1872-1898 (Scrapbook 9)
  - VC 1878 — Botsford, Mary R., 1873-1881 (Scrapbook 10)
  - VC 1878 — Davis, Jennie E., 1873-1883 (Scrapbook 11)
  - VC 1878 — Day, Sarah L., 1874-1878 (Scrapbook 12)
  - VC 1878 — Hubbard, Mary T. [Missing as of November 2022], circa 1878 (Scrapbook 13)
  - VC 1878 — MacLeish, Martha (Hillard), circa 1878 (Scrapbook 14)
  - VC 1878 — McCaleb, Ella, circa 1878 (Scrapbook 15)
  - VC 1878 — Peirce, Lydia (Ray), 1873-1905 (Scrapbook 16)
  - VC 1878 — Woods, Emma E., 1873-1881 (Scrapbook 17)
  - VC 1878-1881 [Special, Music] — Nichols, Gertrude, 1879-1884 (Scrapbook 18)
  - VC 1879 — Edward, Mary (Cookingham), circa 1879 (Scrapbook 19)
  - VC 1879 — Meyer, Marie F. (Baird), 1874-1915 (Scrapbook 215 (Oversize))
  - VC 1879 — Owens, Louise (Benton), 1875-1879 (Scrapbook 20)
  - VC Ex 1879 — Stillwell, Blandina, 1872-1929 (Scrapbook 212 (Oversize))
  - VC 1879 — Windsor, Ethel (Jacobson), 1876-1879 (Scrapbook 22)
  - VC Ex 1880 — Babbott, Lydia (Pratt), 1876-1879 (Scrapbook 23)
  - VC 1880 — Blake, Josephine Dorr, M.D., 1877-1881 (Scrapbook 24)
  - VC 1880 — Class scrapbook [Missing as of November 2022], circa 1880 (Scrapbook 25)
  - VC 1880 — Darling, Katherine, circa 1877-1880 (Scrapbook 26)
  - VC 1880 — Haughwout, Nellie (Preston), 1878-1880 (Scrapbook 27)
  - VC 1880 — Hubbard, Elizabeth (Skinner), 1875-1880 (Scrapbook 28)
  - VC 1880 — Knight, Mariette (Barnes) [Missing as of November 2022], circa 1880 (Scrapbook 29)
  - VC 1880 — Pratt, Mary (Morris), 1875-1880 (Scrapbook 30)
  - VC 1880 — Swan, H. Rachel, 1867-1882 (Scrapbook 31)
  - VC 1880 — Swan, H. Rachel, 1867-1882 (Scrapbook 32)
  - VC 1880-1881 [Preparatory], 1881-1882 [Special] — Brodhead, Fanny (Loveland), 1880-1886 (Scrapbook 21)
  - VC Ex 1881 — Alvord, Evelyn (Fletcher), 1876-1880 (Scrapbook 33)
  - VC 1881 — Barnum, Charlotte C., 1878-1884 (Scrapbook 332 (Oversize))
  - VC Ex 1881 — Hawley, Catherine S., 1877-1901 (Scrapbook 34)
  - VC 1881 — Hayes, Alice, 1876-1888 (Scrapbook 35)
  - VC 1881 — Hodge, E. Carol, 1867-1888 (Scrapbook 36)
  - VC Ex 1881 — Hopson, Katharine Mills, 1877-1881 (Scrapbook 37)
  - VC 1881 — Potter, Cora (Van Benschoten), 1874-1888 (Scrapbook 38)
  - VC 1882 — Broadhead, Stella P., 1879-1890 (Scrapbook 39)
  - VC 1882 — Conable, Mary Florence (Easton), 1882-1884 (Scrapbook 40)
  - VC 1882 — Crawford, Genevieve (Buckland), 1878-1882 (Scrapbook 41)
  - VC 1882 — Wheeler, Jessie F., 1878-1891 (Scrapbook 42)
  - VC 1882 — Wheeler, Jessie F., 1878-1891 (Scrapbook 43)
  - VC 1882 — Wyman, Anne (Southworth), 1878-1882 (Scrapbook 44)
  - VC 1883 — Dewell, Jessie K., 1878-1884 (Scrapbook 45)
  - VC 1883 — Hadley, Helen (Morris), 1878-1888 (Scrapbook 297 (Oversize))
  - VC 1883 — Hopson, Amy S., 1879-1883 (Scrapbook 46)